adultdvdtalk.com 2001-06-06

# Adult DVD Talk Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement for AdultDVDTalk.com**

ChaosUnlimited.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: AdultDVDTalk.com (ADT). 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your comparison cart when using the Price Search features and to gather broad demographic information pertaining to the traffic and use of this web site. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your comparison cart when using the price search and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. The message forum also uses cookies to keep track of your last visit in order to display new messages when you return. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. 

Our site's registration form requires users to provide an email address. We do not require the use of real names on Adult DVD Talk. We may use visitor contact information from the registration form to send the user promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Adult DVD Talk collects email addresses as part of the message forum registration process and to sign up for the ADT Newsletter. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **ADT** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We may use contact data from our surveys to send the user promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We may use contact data from our contests to send users promotional material from some of our partners. We also use this contact information to notify the winners of such contests. A user's contact information is also used to contact them when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

ADT collects statistical information through some visitor actions while using the Price Search function of this web site. This information is stored in a database and used to generate search results, top requested item lists, reports and other data. ADT shares this statistical data with the stores participating in the ADT Price Search. ADT does not share or sell email addresses, user names or any user-specific information with any third parties. 

Violations of ADT's Terms of Use may result in the sharing of any and all information we have with the appropriate authorities to prevent additional violations. 

**Access by Minors**  
This site provides information about products and topics of an adult nature. It is to be used by adults only. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any and all personal information. ADT further suggests that any email communication you may have with individuals that you meet through the use of the chat room or message forum be conducted through anonymous email accounts such as Hotmail, Excite and Yahoo. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. ADT does not store any personal or private information about the users of this site. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [remove@adultdvdtalk.com](mailto:remove@adultdvdtalk.com)

 **Correct/Update** This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@adultdvdtalk.com](mailto:webmaster@adultdvdtalk.com)

 **Contacting the Web Site** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: webmaster@adultdvdtalk.com
